thetaborsoft.com 2016-11-04

# Privacy Policy - TheTaborSoft

This Privacy Policy Document defines the manner in which TheTaborSoft collects, uses as well as maintains and discloses the type of information collected from users (to define each, a “User”) of our website namely www.thetaborsoft.com (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the whole website and all type of services as well as products offered by TheTaborSoft.

**Log Files (Personal Identification Information)**

We have right to collect personal identification information from User/Reader/Visitor in various ways and methods such as when Users visit the website, subscribes to newsletter, submits a form, services and the resources which is availed on our website.

Users have legal right to visit our website anonymously, thus, he/she may visit www.thetaborsoft.com anonymously. We will then collect Personal Identification Information from Anonymous User only if he/she submit such information to us on their own voluntarily.

**Non-Personal Identification Information**

We have right to collected non-personal identification information about User(s)/Visitor(s)/Reader(s)/Subscriber(s), we may collect such information from them in various methods and forms, whenever they interact with our website. Such information may include the browser name (e.g : Google Chrome, Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, etc), Operating System (e.g : Windows, Mac, Linux, Mobile OS, etc) and the ISP (Internet Service Provider) and such other information.

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**Web Browser Cookies and Web Beacons :**

Our website (www.thetaborsoft.com) do use “cookies” to enhance User experience. Web browser places cookies on their hard drive to track information about them and other record-keeping purposes. User is free to choose do special settings in their Web browser to refuse cookies. If you opt to refuse then note that some parts or services of our website may not function.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  1. Google, as a third party partner, uses cookies to serve advertisements on www.thetaborsoft.com
  2. Google uses the DART cookie which enables them to serve advertisements based on their visit to our website and other sites on the Web.
  3. Users may opt out of the use of these DART cookies by visiting the Google advertisement and content network privacy policy page :<http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some other advertising partners may use cookies on our website and they are Google Adsense, Yahoo Ads, Infolinks and Amazon.

These third-party ad networks use special technology to the ads and links that appear on our website which is sent directly to your web browser(s). They automatically receive your Internet Protocol (IP) address when they click on any ad. Some type of other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript and Web Beacons) may also be used by them to enhance user’s experience or for the effectiveness of their ads.

www.thetaborsoft.com has no access and control over third party’s advertisers cookie. However, you can opt out of some if not all at the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website at [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

If necessary you should contact the respective privacy policy of these Ad Servers for more detailed information of their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of these practices.

TheTaborSoft’s privacy policy doesn’t apply to cannot control the activities of such other advertisers or websites.

If you have more questions about our Privacy Policy then please contact us!
